<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Takumi Matsunobu</title>
    <link>https://tkmim.github.io/post/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Takumi Matsunobu</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-gb</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 22 Jan 2022 15:14:07 +0100</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://tkmim.github.io/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Latexdiffcite</title>
      <link>https://tkmim.github.io/post/latexdiffcite/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Nov 2023 20:48:24 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>https://tkmim.github.io/post/latexdiffcite/</guid>
      <description>Setting up latexdiff for trackging changes with citations latexdiffcite is a python wrapper of latexdiff, which makes a track-change tex between given two tex documents taking changes in citations into account.
Source https://github.com/twilsonco/latexdiffcite
https://pypi.org/project/latexdiffcite/
Instalattion Since latexdiffcite is a simple wrapper of latexdiff, the prerequirement is of course latexdiff already installed. Upon that, the easiest way to install latexdiffcite is just using pip like:
pip install latexdiffcite Usage If successfully installed, the one liner below immediately produces diff.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Test</title>
      <link>https://tkmim.github.io/post/test/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Oct 2022 22:48:40 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://tkmim.github.io/post/test/</guid>
      <description>1. はじめに xxxx x. Markdown CheetSheet Text Format Italic（斜体） Italic（斜体） Emphasis（強調） Emphasis（強調） Strikethrough（取</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Style_changelog</title>
      <link>https://tkmim.github.io/post/style_changelog/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Mar 2022 17:01:53 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>https://tkmim.github.io/post/style_changelog/</guid>
      <description>元祖 github-style からの変更履歴 アイコンを日替わりの identicon に設定 (6 March 2022) Publication への固定リンクをメニューに追加 (layout/partials/menu.html) (6 March 2022) ライトモード・ダークモードの切り替えトグルアイ</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Publication</title>
      <link>https://tkmim.github.io/post/publication/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Feb 2022 13:38:14 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>https://tkmim.github.io/post/publication/</guid>
      <description>In preparation/Submitted Matsunobu, T., Puh, M., and Kei, C. (2023) Quantifying flow- and scale-dependent predictability of convective precipitation. under review Peer-reviewed articles Matsunobu, T., Quinting, J. F., Grams, C. M., and Matsueda, M. (2023) Regional extreme precipitation events in wintertime Japan facilitated by East-Asian large-scale flow patterns, SOLA, 19, 253&amp;ndash;260. https://doi.org/10.2151/sola.2023-033.
Matsunobu, T., Keil, C., and Barthlott, C. (2022) The impact of microphysical uncertainty conditional on initial and boundary condition uncertainty under varying synoptic control, Weather Clim.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
